http://www.fortandstone.co.uk/privacy-policy

0 item(s) - £0.00
0Your shopping cart is empty!
Pounds
($)
Canada Dollar
(€)
Euro
(£)
Pounds
($)
US Dollar
£($)
Canada Dollar
(€)
Euro
(£)
Pounds
($)
US Dollar
Face MasksCravatsMen's Paisley CravatsMen's Neat CravatsMen's Spotted CravatsMen's Striped CravatsMen's Country Cravats Various Cravats for MenTiesPaisleyPlain Pure Silk Spotted TiesPure Silk Ties for MenBow TiesSelf-tie Bow TieReady Tie Bow TiesVarious Bow Ties for MenScarvesNeat Scarves for MenPaisley Scarves for MenTown and Country Scarves for MenSpotted Scarves for MenHandkerchiefsPaisleysNeatsSpotsPlainMen's Silk HandkerchiefsWholesale
About
Blog
contact
Contact UsMy AccountWish List (0)CheckoutLoginRegister01252 783091
0 item(s) - £0.00
0Your shopping cart is empty!FACEBOOKpagesPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyFort and Stone Privacy PolicyMaking a Purchase
To purchase any item from our website please simply put the chosen item or items in your shopping cart by clicking add to cart. When you have completed your order go to the checkout page. You will then be asked to provide billing information.
To ensure the security of your payment details Fort and Stone accepts payments via Worldpay - (accepts all major credit and debit cards) and PayPal.
PayPal accepts all major credit and debit cards.Order Confirmation
Once you have placed your order we will confirm receipt of the order by e-mail.Returns Policy
If the goods supplied to you do not arrive in perfect condition, or are damaged in transit, please return them in their original packaging within 7 days of receipt. We will refund you for any faulty or damaged goods including any reasonable postage charges incurred.
We recommend that you keep proof of posting.Privacy Policy
In order to process your order we require certain personal information. Unless you have indicated that you would like to be informed of any special offers or new product information, Fort and Stone will not use this information other than for confirmation and despatch of your order. Fort and Stone does not disclose buyer information to third parties.Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website.
We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website.
Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers.
The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.
Google's privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.Trades Description Act
All effort has been made to ensure that the descriptions and images on this website are as accurate as possible. Nevertheless due to the limitations of web browsers and display monitors, descriptions, images and specifications are published for illustration purposes only and we cannot guarantee that items will look exactly as they appear on your screen.
Prices quoted on our website are inclusive of VAT at the current rate and exclude delivery costs which are specified above.
Errors and omissions are excluded. Your statutory rights are not affected.
Information+Wholesale EnquiriesContact - Fort & StoneDelivery InformationPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsCustomer Service+Wholesale EnquiriesContact UsSign InRegisterSite Map Fort and StoneAbout Fort and Stone Sandy Farm Business Centre
The Sands, Farnham, Surrey, GU10 1PX
01252 783091  Contact Us  Shop NowFort and Stone Wholesale+Wholesale Enquiries+
